<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>D-BAS Feed</title>
        <link>url/static/rss/rss.xml</link>
        <description>Latest news about D-BAS, a Dialog-Based Argumentation System</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 11:24:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <item>
            <title>some new title</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>some new text</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 10:24:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Finding from our fieldtest</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>In the meantime we have finished the evaluation of our first fieldtest, which was done carried
                out to our complete satisfaction. At the moment we are working on our new paper, which will be finished
                soon. Stay tuned!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>HCI in Canada</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Last week we had the chance to introduce our work about embedding dialog-based discussion into
                the real world at the HCI in Vancouver. It was a very huge and broad conference with many interesting
                talks and workshops. Thanks to all listeners during Christians talk.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>First fieldtest</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today we have started our first, real fieldtest, where we invited every student of computer
                science to talk about improvements of our study programme. Our number of students drastic increased
                during the last years, therefore we have to manage some problems like a shortage of space for working
                places and a lack of place classrooms. Our fieldtest will be supported by sociology students, who will
                also do an survey based on our metrics we invented mid 2015.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Docker</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Last weeks we have spend to make D-BAS more stable, writing some analyzers as well as dockerize
                everything. The complete project can be found on https://github.com/hhucn/dbas soon.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Great Test</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Finally we have a version of D-BAS which can be used during a large fieldtest at our
                university. Nevertheless the same version is capable to be viewed by some reviewers of our latest paper.
                Stay tuned!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Experiment</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Last week we finished our second experiment at our professorial chair. In short we are very
                happy with the results and with the first, bigger argumentation map created by inexperienced
                participants! Now we will fix a few smaller things and looking forward to out first field test!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Final version and Captachs</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today we submitted a journal paper about D-BAS and its implementation at Springers CSCW.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Final version and Captachs</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>We have a delayed christmas present for you. D-BAS reached it's first final version including
                reCAPTCHAS and several minor fixes!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Work goes on</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>After the positive feedback at COMMA16, we decided to do a first field tests with D-BAS at our
                university. Therefore we are working on current issues, so that we will releasing v1.0. soon.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMMA16</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Based on the hard work of the last month, we are attending the 6th International Conference on
                Computational Models of Argument (COMMA16) in Potsdam. There we are going to show the first demo of
                D-BAS and present the paper of Krauthoff T., Betz G., Baurmann M. &amp; Mauve, M. (2016) "Dialog-Based
                Online Argumentation". Looking forward to see you!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Review Process</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Our first version of the review-module is now online. Every confronting argument can be flagged
                regarding a specific reason now. Theses flagged argument will be reviewed by other participants, who
                have enough reputation. Have a look at the review-section!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Review Process</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>I regret that i have neglected the news section, but this is in your interest. In the meantime
                we are working on an graph view for our argumentation model, a review section for statements and we are
                improving the ways how we act with each kind of user input. Stay tuned!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sidebar</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today we released a new text-based sidebar for a better experience. Have fun!</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMMA16</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>We are happy to announce, that our paper for the COMMA16 was accepted. In the meantime many
                little improvements as well as first user tests were done.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>History Management</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>We have changed D-BAS' history management. Now you can bookmark any link in any discussion and
                your history will always be with you!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Development is going on</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Recently we improved some features, which will be released in future. Firstly there will be an
                island view for every argument, where the participants can see every premise for current reactions.
                Secondly the opinion barometer is still under development. For a more recent update, have a look at our
                imprint.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMMA16</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>After much work, testing and debugging, we now have version of D-BAS, which will be submitted
                to &lt;a href="http://www.ling.uni-potsdam.de/comma2016" target="_blank"&gt;COMMA 2016&lt;/a&gt;.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Speech Bubble System</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>After one week of testing, we released a new minor version of D-BAS. Instead of the text
                presentation,we will use chat-like style :) Come on and try it! Additionally anonymous users will have a
                history now!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Notification System</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Yesterday we have develope a minimal notification system. This system could send information to
                every author, if one of their statement was edited. More features are coming soon!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Premisegroups</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Now we have a mechanism for unclear statements. For example the user enters "I want something
                because A and B". The we do not know, whether A and B must hold at the same time, or if she wants
                something when A or B holds. Therefore the system requests feedback.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>API</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Now D-BAS has an API. Just replace the "discuss"-tag in your url with api to get your current
                steps raw data.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Refactoring</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>D-BAS refactored the last two weeks. During this time, a lot of JavaScript was removed.
                Therefore D-BAS uses Chameleon with TAL in the Pyramid-Framework. So D-BAS will be more stable and
                faster. The next period all functions will be tested and recovered.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Island View and Pictures</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>D-BAS will be more personal and results driven. Therefore the new release has profile pictures
                for everyone. They are powered by gravatar and are based on a md5-hash of the users email. Next to this
                a new view was published - the island view. Do not be shy and try it in discussions ;-) Last improvement
                just collects the attacks and supports for arguments...this is needed for our next big thing :) Stay
                tuned!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Voting Model</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Currently we are improving out model of voting for arguments as well as statements. Therefore
                we are working together with our colleagues from the theoretical computer science... because D-BAS data
                structure can be formalized to be compatible with frameworks of Dung.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Happy new Year</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Frohes Neues Jahr ... Bonne Annee ... Happy New Year ... Feliz Ano Nuevo ... Feliz Ano Novo
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Piwik</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today Piwik was installed. It will help to improve the services of D-BAS!</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Logic improvements</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Every week we try to improve the look and feel of the discussions navigation. Sometimes just a
                few words are edited, but on other day the logic itself gets an update. So keep on testing :)
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Breadcrumbs</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Now we have a breadcrumbs with shortcuts for every step in our discussion. This feature will be
                im improved soon!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Improved Bootstrapping</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Bootstraping is one of the main challenges in discussion. Therefore we have a two-step process
                for this task!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Design Update</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today we released a new material-oriented design. Enjoy it!</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Stable release</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>After two weeks of debugging, a first and stable version is online. Now we can start with the
                interesting things!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Different topics</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Since today we can switch between different topics :) Unfortunately this feature is not really
                tested ;-)
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New logic for inserting</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Logic for inserting statements was redone. Every time, where the user can add information via a
                text area, only the area is visible, which is logically correct. Therefore the decisions are based on
                argumentation theory.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Anonymous users after vacation</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>After two and a half week of vacation we have a new feature. The discussion is now available
                for anonymous users, therefore everyone can participate, but only registered users can make and edit
                statements.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Vacation done</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>After two and a half weeks of vacation a new feature was done. Hence anonymous users can
                participate, the discussion is open for all, but committing and editing statements is for registered
                users only.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New URL-Schemes</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Now D-BAS has unique urls for the discussion, therefore these urls can be shared.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Long time, no see!</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>In the mean time we have developed a new, better, more logically data structure. Additionally
                the navigation was refreshed.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>i18n/l10n</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Internationalization is now working :)</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>i18n</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Still working on i18n-problems of chameleon templates due to lingua. If this is fixed, i18n of
                jQuery will happen. Afterwards l10n will take place.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Design &amp; Research</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>D-BAS is still under construction. Meanwhile the index page was recreated and we are improving
                our algorithm for the guided view mode. Next to this we are inventing a bunch of metrics for measuring
                the quality of discussion in several software programs.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Session Management / CSRF</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>D-BAS is no able to manage a session as well as it has protection against CSRF.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Edit/Changelog</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Now, each user can edit positions and arguments. All changes will be saved and can be watched.
                Future work is the chance to edit the relations between positions.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Simple Navigation was improved</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Because the first kind of navigation was finished recently, D-BAS is now dynamically. That
                means, that each user can add positions and arguments on his own.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Open issues&lt;/i&gt;
                are i18n, a framework for JS-tests as well as the content of the popups.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Simple Navigation ready</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>First beta of D-BAS navigation is now ready. Within this kind the user will be permanently
                confronted with arguments, which have a attack relation to the current selected argument/position. For
                an justification the user can select out of all arguments, which have a attack relation to the
                'attacking' argument. Unfortunately the support-relation are currently useless except for the
                justification for the position at start.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Admin Interface</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Everything is growing, we have now a little admin interface and a navigation for the discussion
                is finished, but this is very basic and simple
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sharing</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Every news can now be shared via FB, G+, Twitter and Mail. Not very important, but in some kind
                it is...
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Workshop</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today: A new workshop at the O.A.S.E. :)</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tests and JS</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Front-end tests with Splinter are now finished. They are great and easy to manage. Additionally
                I'am working on JS, so we can navigate in a static graph. Next to this, the I18N is waiting...
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>JS Starts</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Today started the funny part about the dialog based part, embedded in the content page.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>No I18N + L10N</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Interationalization and localization is much more difficult than described by pyramid. This has
                something todo with Chameleon 2, Lingua and Babel, so this feature has to wait.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>I18N + L10N</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>D-BAS, now with internationalization and translation.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Settings</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>New part of the website is finished: a settings page for every user.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>About the Workshop in Karlsruhe</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>The workshop was very interesting. We have had very interesting talks and got much great
                feedback vom Jun.-Prof. Dr. Betz and Mr. Voigt. A repetition will be planed for the middle of july.
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Workshop in Karlsruhe</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>The working group 'functionality' will drive to Karlsruhe for a workshop with Jun.-Prof. Dr.
                Betz as well as with C. Voigt until 08.05.2015. Our main topics will be the measurement of quality of
                discussions and the design of online-participation. I think, this will be very interesting!
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>First set of tests</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Finished first set of unit- and integration tests for the database and frontend.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Page is growing</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>The contact page is now working as well as the password-request option.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>System will be build up</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>Currently I am working a lot at the system. This work includes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;frontend-design
                with CSS and jQuery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;backend-development with pything&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;development
                of unit- and integration tests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;a database scheme&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;validating and
                deserializing data with &lt;a href="http://docs.pylonsproject.org/projects/colander/en/latest/"&gt;Colander&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;translating
                string with &lt;a
                href="http://docs.pylonsproject.org/projects/pyramid/en/latest/narr/i18n.html#localization-deployment-settings"&gt;internationalization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>First mockup</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>The webpage has now a contact, login and register site.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Start</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>I've started with the Prototype.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>First steps</title>
            <link>https://dbas.cs.uni-duesseldorf.de/news</link>
            <description>I've started with with my PhD.</description>
            <author>Tobias Krauthoff</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>